

Tien LE CONG

FRESHER FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

✓ letien18102001@gmail.com

- ★ Go Vap District, Ho Chi Minh
- m Date of birth 10/18/2001
- https://lecongtien.vercel.app/
- 03 93 92 34 19

CERTIFICATIONS

English: CEF B1 - May 2022 Front-End Website Developer: Cybersoft Academy - Oct 2022

Skills

Techs

Git, MySQL, SQL Server, PostgreSQL, Redis, Docker

Front-end

HTML/CSS: HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind,

SCSS, Responsive

Javascript: ReactJS, Typescript,

ES6, AJax, Jquery

Back-end

Java: Web Servlet, Spring Boot, Hibernate, Restful Api, Spring Security, Caching Data Node JS: ExpressJS, ORM (Sequelize, Prisma), Nest JS, Swagger, GraphQL, SocketIO



OBJECTIVE

With my experience in **ReactJS** as a Front-end developer and Back-end developer with **Java Spring Boot** and **Node JS**, I am confident that I can assist your company and excited to bring new ideas to your team **Short-term**: Learn more English.

Short-term. Learn more English.

Long-term: Become a Senior Full-stack

EDUCATION

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology

Since September 2019

Major: Information Technology

GPA current: 3.61/4.0

Cybersoft Center Coure

From June 2022 to November 2022

Front-End Web Developer

GPA: 8.5/10 | Knowledge: ReactJS, TypeScript

Work experience

Hitachi Vantara

Since April 2023 Full-stack Developer (Intern)

Main responsibilities: Join the training course and participate in the Full-stack Management System project.

Description: Project to support employee management

Tech: Front-end: Scss, Reactjs, Ant Design, TypeScript Back-end: Java Spring Boot and Spring Security, Postgres.

Main works:

- Build UI and integrate API and logic.
- Analyze, organize, store and retrieve data on a database
- Create restful API and use JWT library for authentication
- Import file excel and write Unit tests

REFERENCES

₱ @https://github.com/Cong-Tien

Work experience

BOOKING MOVIE (PET PROJECT)

From August 2022 to October 2022

Front-end and Back-end Developer

Description: a commercial website to sell movie tickets.

Tech:

- Front-end: Scss, Tailwind, Reactjs, Ant Design, Redux Thunk.
- Back-end: Java, MySQL, Hibernate, Spring Boot and Spring Security, Redis, Socket IO.

Main works:

- Build UI and integrate API and logic.
- Improve performance website: useMemo, useCallback,...
- Analyze, organize, store and retrieve data on a database
- Create restful api with spring boot and use JWT library for authentication and authorization
- Caching data to optimize data access speed and build realtime feature when customers buy tickets, login facebook.

Link git: https://github.com/Cong-

<u>Tien/CinemaReactJava</u>

Link demo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?

v=0oOC-FwlVHw

♦ WEBSITE ADVERTISING MOVIE(PET PROJECT)

From October 2022 to December 2023

Front-end and Back-end Developer

Description: Movie ticket sales system website **Tech**:

- Front-end: Scss, Tailwind, Reactjs, Redux Thunk, Ant Design, TypeScript
- Back-end: Nodejs, Nest JS, ORM(Prisma), Swagger, Socket IO

Main works:

- Build UI and integrate API and logic
- Analyze, organize, store and retrieve data on a database
- Create restful API and use JWT library for authentication

Link git front-end: https://github.com/Cong-

<u>Tien/CinemaReactJava</u>

Link git back-end: https://github.com/Cong-

<u>Tien/CinemaNodejs</u>